Characters, actions, places, occupations,
and events in this series
are fictional and created
for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge
or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
If you want to be my sugar baby…
You are mine only.
But it doesn’t mean
that I will have only you.
You need to help me get Chan back.
Otherwise, I won’t help you
with the debt you owe me.
Hi.
Do you miss me?
From now on, making you smile
will be my main duty.
Who is this girl?
Just say what you want to say.
Come on, sis.
Why are you in such a hurry?
I just want to get to know your girl.
Please take good care of my sister.
She can be stern, hotheaded,
and irritable sometimes.
But she’s actually a sweet person.
No matter what she is like,
I can handle her.
She has the confidence.
I like her.
This is the kind of girl
who can handle you.
Sister.
You have my approval.
Thank you.
I’ll do my best.
You should leave.
Don’t try to get rid of me.
What do you want to talk to me about?
I came to see you today
because I want to talk to you about Jay.
I think she wants to get back with you.
But I don’t want it to happen.
Can you promise me
that you won’t get back with her?
Aren’t you hurt enough because of her?
Can you stop talking about her, Sun?
No.
I won’t stop.
I don’t want to see you
falling apart again.
Sun.
You should leave.
You too.
I want to be alone tonight.
How long are you going to stay, Miss?
Indefinitely.
It’s our pleasure.
What are you doing here?
I just want to try your hotel service.
Your hotel is the best, right?
You should stay at another hotel.
I’ll arrange it for you.
No.
I’m going to stay here.
I don’t know what you are planning.
But it’s not going to happen.
You can’t run away from me, Chan.
I’m going to get back with you.
You and I can never really be over.
I’m asking you.
Don’t cause a problem at my hotel.
I’m not here to cause a problem.
I stay here because of work.
I want to monitor the restaurant
to make sure everything is in order.
Okay?
Is that all?
Okay.
Welcome to the Crescent.
Jay.
Don’t you think
you’re coming on a little too strong?
You are making Chan uncomfortable.
You know her well.
If I don’t do this,
I will never get her back.
From now on, I’ll discuss the details
of the restaurant opening with Chan.
You just set up a meeting with her for me.
But this is also my restaurant.
I want to attend the meeting as well.
Sorry.
You don’t need to attend it.
Just make an appointment for me.
You can go now.
I’ll hurry to pay you back
as soon as possible.
When I fully pay you back,
just so we’re clear,
I will not help you with Chan anymore.
If Chan refuses to get back with you,
I want you to move on.
Don’t worry about that.
I will make her love me again.
Can I drink it too?
Jay.
Why are you that surprised?
You suddenly pop up. So I’m taken aback.
Can I?
Sure. You can drink it first.
I mean, we should drink it together.
How?
You drink it first.
Come on.
(Hurry up.)
(You know what.)
(I thought you liked boys.)
(Because of you,)
(I realized that I like girls.)
(What if one day I change my mind
and like a boy?)
It’s okay.
(As long as you like me right now,
that's enough for me.)
Chan, it’s time to move on.
Don’t be a fool.
Can you come to see me?
Thank you for buying me
an entire new wardrobe.
No need to thank me.
You are my sugar baby.
It’s too bad.
The shop doesn’t sell nightgowns.
Right?
Nightgowns.
I don’t think you need them.
You’re right.
I don’t need them.
You’re such a perv.
Didn’t you say you’re changing
my fashion style?
Don’t my nightgowns
need to be changed too?
You should go to work.
You’ll be late.
Aren’t you going to watch me sing tonight?
No.
I've reached my limit
for spending time with people for today.
Where am I going to put those clothes?
I can take them to my condo first.
I can move in with you.
So I don’t have to
take them back to my home.
You should go to work.
Alright.
Thank you so much.
I had a great time today.
Bye.
♪ The way you touch me here tonight ♪
♪ Makes my feelings come alive ♪
♪ When you come close
I hear your heartbeat ♪
♪ My heart is racing, feeling the heat ♪
♪ You tell me I should never kiss you ♪
♪ Scared it could get dangerous ♪
♪ But every time you tell me no ♪
♪ You only make me lose control ♪
♪ Let every rhythm, yours and mine ♪
♪ Move in sync,
let our hearts come alive ♪
♪ The closer we get,
I can’t resist a kiss ♪
♪ Just follow what you feel, my Red Kiss ♪
♪ Let this be the rhythm,
yours and mine, ohh ♪
♪ The closer we are,
I can’t resist a kiss ♪
♪ Just follow what you feel, my Red Kiss ♪
Why are you so dressed up today, Key?
Someone bought me this dress.
Someone bought it for you?
Who?
Hold on.
You never let anyone tell you
what to wear.
Why are you letting her do that?
Look at her.
I guess you are serious about this one.
Stop teasing me.
Don’t you have to go home?
Won’t your partner call looking for you?
I’m not going home.
I need to get all the tea on you first.
What?
So?
Are you going to listen to my tea?
Or go home?
Fine, I’ve got to go.
Why? Are you afraid of your girlfriend?
No.
-I’m leaving.
-Me too.
See you.
You are a talented singer.
Hi.
Have a seat.
We run into each other quite often,
as you said.
Don’t you think
we should tell each other our names?
No, I like it this way.
Do you like things to be mysterious?
It’s fun.
You are afraid that
you will fall for me, aren’t you?
No.
Are you worried about that?
No, I already have someone I like.
What about you?
Do you have one?
Yes.
But there’s a problem.
She is really mad at me.
But it’s my fault.
Why don’t you try to make up with her?
I’m trying.
But it’s very hard.
If you can’t move on from her,
you need to do everything
so you can go on with her.
Even if it means
you need to change yourself,
you need to do it.
So you can be with her.
If I can’t be myself, is that a good idea?
It’s the price you have to pay.
Sometimes,
for love,
we have to do it.
I like what you said.
I get it now.
I’m rooting for you.
Hello.
Right now?
Sure.
I’ll be right there.
I’ve got to go.
I’m rooting for you.
Bye.
Good luck.
Can you give me another chance, Chan?
Chan, I’m here.
Chan.
Are you playing hide-and-seek with me,
pretty sis?
Chan.
You got caught, little perv.
You caught me.
What are you going to do to me?
I will…
give you a penalty.
Do you want me to take a shower first?
You still smell good.
Chan.
Jay.
How did you get in here?
You.
You…
You are Chan’s ex?
Chan.
Is she your new girlfriend?
She’s not my girlfriend.
It’s complicated.
How did you get in?
You gave me your keycard.
I’ve never thrown it away.
So what is your relationship with her?
She’s just my sugar baby.
Now I get it
why I don’t want to tell you my name.
I don’t think we can be friends.
Did you meet Key before?
So your name is Key.
You should leave.
I want to talk to my girlfriend.
Didn’t you break up?
What right do you have
to tell me to leave?
Right now,
Chan is no longer your girlfriend.
Neither are you.
That’s enough.
Both of you.
Chan.
You and I need to talk.
You have no right to tell me what to do.
We broke up.
Don’t you remember?
You should leave.
I’ll see you.
You should leave too.
But…
You have no right.
Don’t forget your status.
KEY
Come in.
Miss Chan.
Mr. Phu is here to see you.
Please come in.
Chan.
I’m sorry.
I shouldn’t have asked Jay for help.
It’s too late, Phu.
Let it slide.
I’m not mad at you about that.
I’m mad at you
because when you have a problem,
you never come to me.
I didn’t want you
to be disappointed in me.
But you are disappointing me right now.
Forget it.
You need to do everything
to make Jay leave this hotel.
That’s the problem.
Jay told me
she needs to see you right now.
She gave me an ultimatum.
You need to go to see her.
She will leave…
only when you tell her to leave.
She will not leave, Phu.
Never.
What’s wrong, little rascal?
Why aren’t you eating?
You’re looking so down.
It’s nothing.
I’m okay.
You’re okay?
You’re so not okay.
I’m really okay, Peach.
I swear.
You’re lying.
I’m not lying.
When you lie, you always avoid
looking me in the eye.
I’m not doing that.
Will you tell me or not?
Huh?
Fine, I’ll tell you.
I’m so tired of how you catch me lying.
I’ve been using this method
since you were five.
It always works.
This is cheating.
You can't tell anyone about it.
Otherwise, I’ll be mad at you.
I won’t tell anyone.
So I can have all the fun to myself.
But you told Dad, Big Mom, and Aunt Niam.
Alright.
So what is your problem?
Why did you cry?
How did you know I cried?
Your eyes are all swollen.
Anyone can tell
that you were crying all night.
Do you want some wine?
Can you stop doing this?
Doing this?
Doing what?
You always have to get things your way.
You know me well.
I’m asking you.
Please leave my hotel.
I won’t leave
until you get back with me.
Do you think doing this
will help you get me back?
You know I don’t care about methods.
All I care about is the result.
I will do everything to get you back.
I really miss you, you know?
We broke up a long time ago, Jay.
Please don’t do this.
But I’m back now.
I came back to you.
I will never leave again.
I promise.
We will go back to how we were before.
Walk slowly.
A little further.
A bit further.
Can I open my eyes now?
Three.
Two.
One.
You bought me a piano.
Why did you do that?
I bought it to show how much I love you.
Thank you.
(I promise)
(I will take good care of your piano.)
Of course, I like it.
(It’s not my piano.)
It’s our piano.
It sounds amazing.
Thank you.
I love you so much.
You are my first love, Chan.
Chan.
You’re up?
Did I wake you up?
You need to take responsibility for it.
Hold me.
Come here.
Jay.
I’m home.
I bought snacks for you.
Jay.
I'M SORRY.
—J.
It’s true that we are
each other’s first love.
For me,
our relationship ended a long time ago.
I can’t accept it.
I know you still love me.
You can’t run away from me, Chan.
You can’t run away from your feelings.
Please give me another chance.
Please.
I’m sorry.
No.
No, please.
Please
Peach.
Please say something.
What do you want me to say?
Don’t worry, Peach.
How can I not be worried?
What are you thinking?
Why did you agree to be her sugar baby?
If Dad and Big Mom find out,
they will be crushed.
Then don’t tell them.
Please, Peach.
Why are you doing this, Key?
You agreed to be Chan’s sugar baby.
Is it because of Mom?
No.
You’re lying.
You are doing this
because you think
you don’t deserve her, don’t you?
Key.
You are my sister.
For me, you are very important.
Everyone in our family
also feels the same way.
I know.
But I…
I don’t feel confident.
It’s okay, my little sis.
So…
What should I do about Chan?
Fight for her.
If you think you can’t move on from her,
then you need to do everything
so you can go on with her.
You didn’t do anything wrong.
You didn’t steal her from anyone.
Come on.
If you think Chan is the one for you,
then go for it.
Why did you stop?
I want you to know this.
It’s my job.
What job?
I’ll help you forget her.
From now on,
you will remember only me.
Thank you.
I’m so sorry
for putting you through this.
It’s okay.
Can you hold me like this all night?
Sure.
I will hold you through the night.
I love you.
Even though…
you still don’t love me, it’s okay.
But I will always love you.
I won’t leave you.
Thank you.
I’m sorry.
I’m so sorry.
You are just her sugar baby.
But a sugar baby like me,
I’ve never hurt her.
Chan, do you have any song
you want me to sing?
The song that you sang that night.
About Key? Are you just sleeping with her,
or are you serious about her?
I admit it. I still love you, Jay.
I did some digging about you.
You come from a well-known family.
Why did you agree to be Chan’s sugar baby?
If I tell you,
will you get out of Chan’s life?